peopleadmin.com 2019-04-06

# PeopleAdmin Privacy Policy - PeopleAdmin

Skip to content

    *     * Explore PeopleAdmin’s software tools designed to help colleges and universities attract, and hire top faculty and staff.

    * Onboard & Manage Solutions

See PeopleAdmin’s tools proven to simplify onboarding, recordkeeping and position management.

    * Develop & Retain Solutions

Discover how PeopleAdmin’s performance management system supports employee and institutional success.

  * RESOURCES
  * ABOUT
  * SUPPORT
  * 

PeopleAdmin Privacy Policy[Damon Tribble](https://www.peopleadmin.com/author/damon/ "Posts by Damon Tribble")2018-11-19T11:26:17+00:00

PeopleAdmin is a leading provider of Human Resource solutions specifically designed for institutions of Higher Education. PeopleAdmin solutions are delivered as a vendor-hosted SaaS (Software-as-a-Service) model, meaning that we host the information on behalf of all of the clients under contract with PeopleAdmin (each a “Customer”), all of whom act as “data controllers.”

PeopleAdmin does not have any right to disclose confidential information to any third party, except as required by law or at the request of the Customer.

PeopleAdmin utilizes reasonable industry standard technology to secure Customer information including the use of SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption in transferring client data; multi-level firewalls to prevent external intrusion; frequent backups of Customer data; and a fully redundant hardware platform to ensure system availability.

## Information Collection and Use

PeopleAdmin is configured to the unique needs of each Customer, in this case also the “data controller,” and is designed to carry out procedures as specified by the Customer. PeopleAdmin software is typically used to automate the hiring, onboarding, and performance assessment of applicants and employees.

The Customer or data controller is responsible for determining what data is collected in the PeopleAdmin system and how that information is utilized and processed in various organizational business processes.  Some collected data may be used to make automated decisions, all of which are determined by the Customer.

PeopleAdmin makes no attempt to determine or advise as to whether the Customer’s procedures comply with any statutory or regulatory requirements, including but not limited to any statutory or regulatory requirements related to hiring, employment, race, color, ancestry, religion, citizenship, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, pregnancy, veteran status, national origin, disability, or any federal, state or local statutes governing the employer/employee relationship. The collection and processing of personal information is solely up to the discretion of the customer or data controller.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

We also respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process (such as law enforcement requests), or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of PeopleAdmin, Inc.’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

## Cookies

PeopleAdmin.com may set and access PeopleAdmin cookies on your computer. Our website utilizes cookies to create a more customized experience for our users and customers. For example, we use tracking pixels (i.e. Google Analytics) to aid in measuring and tracking where our website traffic is coming from and to track the performance of our site. We use remarking pixels from Google to aid in customized, targeted followup advertising.

PeopleAdmin solutions do not access cookies within the applications.

## Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

PeopleAdmin utilizes industry standard technology to secure customer information including the use of SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption in transferring client data; multi-level firewalls to prevent external intrusion; frequent backups of customer data; and a fully redundant hardware platform to ensure system availability.

## Changes to this Policy

PeopleAdmin, Inc. may update this policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your PeopleAdmin, Inc. account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

## Acceptance

By using the Solution you signify your acceptance of this Policy, as amended from time to time. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions contained in this policy, please do not use the Solution.

## Contact Information

If you have thoughts, questions or suggestions about PeopleAdmin’s Privacy Policy, please contact email us at [privacy@peopleadmin.com](mailto:privacy@peopleadmin.com).

￼

## To learn more about PeopleAdmin’s GDPR compliance, download our FAQ page.

Send this to a friend

Your emailRecipient email
